<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aktuelles on Seebrücke Ismaning</title>
    <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aktuelles on Seebrücke Ismaning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cayman Typography</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/cayman-typography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/cayman-typography/</guid>
      <description>Text Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
Paragraph There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interessante Links</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Interessante Links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kontakt</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Möchtest du mehr erfahren oder hast du Lust dich zu engagieren?
Schreib uns eine Mail auf ismaning@seebruecke.org!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sicherer Hafen Ismaning</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/demands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/demands/</guid>
      <description>Tausende Geflüchtete erleben jeden Tag an den Außengrenzen Europas Zustände, die mit dem demokratischen, im Grundgesetz verankerten Selbstverständnis unseres Rechtsstaates nicht vereinbar sind. Sie sind von illegalen Pushbacks betroffen oder müssen in Sammellagern unter unwürdigen Bedingungen leben.
So ist, nach dem verheerenden Brand im Sammellager Moria, die Zahl der Einwohner des Nachfolgecamps auf 7000 (Stand: November 2020) gestiegen. Den Betroffenen fehlt jegliche Perspektive, obwohl deutsche Asylanträge letztes Jahr auf ein Rekordtief der letzten 8 Jahre gefallen ist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Über uns</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Etwas über uns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katex Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/katex-math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/katex-math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>Enable Katex in the config file by setting the katex param to true. This will import the necessary Katex CSS/JS.
See the online reference of supported TeX functions.
Note: For inline math to render correctly, your content file extension must be .mmark. See the official mmark site.
Inline math: $$ \varphi = \dfrac{1+\sqrt5}{2}= 1.6180339887… $$ Inline math: \( \varphi = \dfrac{1+\sqrt5}{2}= 1.6180339887… \)
Block math: $$ \varphi = 1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\cdots} } } $$ Block math:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Images</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/nasa-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/nasa-images/</guid>
      <description>The below images are from the NASA Image and Video Library &amp;ndash; indulge yourself, revel in their beauty. Also, the built-in figure shortcode is shown for each image.
 {{&amp;lt; figure img=&amp;quot;sun.jpg&amp;quot; caption=&amp;quot;The Sun is the star at the center of the Solar System. It is a nearly perfect sphere of hot plasma, with internal convective motion that generates a magnetic field via a dynamo process. It is by far the most important source of energy for life on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://seebruecke-ismaning.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/▾ images/logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/▾ static/▾ images/logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
